handofthegods.com 2017-06-22

# Hi-Rez Studios® Online Privacy Policy

                                   Hi-Rez Studios® Online Privacy Policy
                                      Last updated on August 20, 2015.
THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY (the “Privacy Policy”) sets forth certain terms and conditions pursuant to
which Hi-Rez Studios, Inc. (“Hi-Rez,” “we,” “us,” or "our") may collect, store, and use certain information
and data concerning or provided by you or authorized users of your Account with Hi-Rez (collectively,
“you” or “your”) in connection with your access or use of the Site (as defined below) or any games that are
made available via our Site ("Game" or "Games"), and any related services (collectively with the Site and
Games, the "Services"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to information or data that may be collected
by Hi-Rez offline. This Privacy Policy applies to the following websites operated by Hi-Rez and any such
other websites established by Hi-Rez or its subsidiaries from time to time which reference this Privacy
Policy (collectively, the “Site”):
        Hi-Rez Studios®
             o <http://www.hirez.com>
             o < http://www.hirezstudios.com>
             o < http://game.hirezstudios.com>
             o < http://account.hirezstudios.com>
        Global Agenda®
             o < http://www.globalagendagame.com>
             o <http://www.globalassault.com>
             o <http://www.globalassaultgame.com>
        Tribes Universe™
             o < http://www.tribesuniverse.com>
        Tribes: Ascend®
             o < http://www.tribesascend.com>
        SMITE®
             o <http://www.smitegame.com>
             o <http://esports.smitegame.com>
        Paladins™
             o <http://www.paladins.com>
             o <http://www.paladinsgame.com>
        Jetpack Fighter®
             o <http://www.jetpackfighter.com>
        GameVid Expo™
             o <http://www.gamevidexpo.com>
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of Hi-Rez’s Online Terms of Service and Use
Agreement. You understand and agree that by accessing and/or using the Services, you are
agreeing to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy.
NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME, SO PLEASE CHECK BACK
REGULARLY TO STAY INFORMED OF ANY CHANGES. MATERIAL CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY
POLICY MAY BE POSTED ON THE SITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICES, INCLUDING

ANY ACCESS TO YOUR ACCOUNT, FOLLOWING ANY SUCH CHANGES, CONSTITUTES AND
SIGNIFIES YOUR FULL ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES.
Consent
BY USING THE SERVICES, INCLUDING ANY OF OUR WEBSITES OR GAMES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR
CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE
DO NOT USE THE SERVICES. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES IN AND TO THIS
PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME. PLEASE CHECK THE PRIVACY POLICY EACH TIME YOU USE THE
SERVICES TO ENSURE YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY PRACTICES. THE
PRIVACY POLICY WILL INDICATE THE DATE IT WAS LAST UPDATED. ALSO, IF THERE IS A
SUBSTANTIVE CHANGE IN THE WAY THAT WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE MAY
NOTIFY YOU VIA E-MAIL OF THE RELEVANT CHANGES. IF YOU CHOOSE TO OPT-OUT OF OUR
CHANGED PRACTICE, OUR E-MAIL MAY CONTAIN INSTRUCTIONS ON HOW TO OPT-OUT, OR YOU
MAY E-MAIL OUR DATA PRIVACY OFFICER AT ANY TIME AT PRIVACY@HIREZSTUDIOS.COM.
YOUR CONTINUED USE OR PARTIAL USE OF THE SERVICES, INCLUDING ANY OF OUR
WEBSITES OR GAMES, WILL SIGNIFY AND BE DEEMED TO CONSTITUTE YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF
ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
Privacy Statement
Hi-Rez respects the privacy of its online visitors and recognizes the importance of protecting the
information collected about you. We have adopted a company-wide Privacy Policy that guides how we
collect, store, and use the information you provide online. This Privacy Policy applies to all aspects of the
Services, including both to persons who register or establish an account with Hi-Rez and to casual
browsers of our websites.
If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our Privacy Policy or use of your
information, please contact our Data Privacy Officer at privacy@hirezstudios.com.
In addition, Hi-Rez owns several other domain names that link or point to the websites listed above, and
we will from time to time add new websites that may or may not be listed above. Please note that this
Privacy Policy applies only to the websites maintained by Hi-Rez, and not to websites maintained by third
parties to which the websites listed above may link.
Third Party Websites
If you click on a link to a third party website, including, without limitation, any third party payment services
or other services offered through the Site or any advertisement or link to an online advertising company,
you will leave the Hi-Rez website you are visiting and go to the website you selected. For example, you
may be required to establish a STEAM account with Valve Corporation to use a Game, and you may be
required to provide credit card and other information to Valve Corporation and our other third party
payment processors when you make any purchase through the Services. Because we cannot control the
activities of third parties, including third party payment service providers and other service providers, we
cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot
guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as Hi-Rez. IF YOU VISIT A
THIRD PARTY WEBSITE THAT IS LINKED TO THE SITE, YOU SHOULD CONSULT THAT WEBSITE’S
PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE PROVIDING ANY PERSONAL OR OTHER INFORMATION. We also
encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request
services.
What is Personal Information and When Does Hi-Rez Collect It?
Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you online or offline. Hi-
Rez collects personal information on a voluntary basis. Online visitors typically submit information to Hi-
Rez through (1) use or partial use of the Services (2) the purchase of goods or services through the

Services, (3) use of our software or online services (including, without limitation, when you register for an
account with Hi-Rez), (4) participation in message boards and contests (including, without limitation, in
connection with registering and claiming prizes), (5) warranty registration, (6) customer support or
technical service requests, (7) player match-up or other online services, (8) registration for Games or
special Game-specific event participation, (9) marketing surveys and e-mail campaigns, (10) requests for
services from third party service providers on our websites, (11) surveys and newsletters, and (12)
consumer complaints.
Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, e-mail address,
phone number, mobile number, home address, birth date, credit card information, and other personal
information as defined under applicable law. We do not require this information to gain access to the Site;
however, you may not use certain features, products, or services (including, without limitation, the
Services) that require registration, or receive materials (e.g., newsletters), unless such information is
provided. You hereby consent to our collection of your personal information as outlined herein.
Other Information Collected
Certain activities will require you to create a username and password and provide other, non-personal
information such as your age, date of birth, gender, game, and other preferences, etc. In addition, we may
collect demographic and other information without notice, such as gender, zip code, information about
your computer, mobile device, tablet, console, handheld device, hardware, software, platform, media,
Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and connection, information about online activity (e.g., feature usage, etc),
gameplay statistics and scores, user rankings, and click paths and other data that you may provide in
surveys or online profiles. We may also combine demographic and other information with personal
information. Prize winners may also be required to provide Social Security or Social Identification
Numbers for tax purposes.
When you use the Services, we may retrieve information about your hardware, software, gameplay, and
how our Games are used, including, without limitation, your Internet Protocol Address, your gameplay
characteristics and patterns, etc. We use this information to enable you to play our Games over the
Internet. We also use this information to better understand the behavior and preferences of our customers
so that we can improve our products and services.
Online Chat Rooms, Forums, and Profiles
You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online message boards, chat rooms,
forums, or in creating user “profiles” when you use the Services. Information that you disclose in message
boards, chat rooms, forums, or in “profile” information is public information, and there is no expectation of
privacy or confidentiality. Please see our Online Terms of Service and Use Agreement on this point and
for other guidelines about posting content on our websites.
Public Data
Your participation in online tournaments or other online Game events is conditional upon your agreement
to us collecting, using, storing, transmitting, and publicly displaying statistical data (e.g., your scores,
rankings, and achievements) generated through your participation in the foregoing.
A Special Note About Children
Hi-Rez does not permit access to the Site by children under the age of thirteen. If you are under thirteen
years of age, you should not access, or attempt to obtain access to, any of the Hi-Rez websites. Once a
child states that his or her age is under thirteen, we do not collect or store any personally identifiable
information such as name, address, or email address. Teenagers under the age of eighteen and over the
age of twelve should encourage their parents to review this Privacy Policy and to contact us if they would
like to raise any concerns.

What About Cookies and Other Technologies?
We may use cookies and other technologies to collect demographic and other information, personalize
your experience with the Services, and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small
files downloaded to your computer to track movements and behavior within websites. Certain of our
websites may use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you do not see the same ad
repeatedly. Also, we may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes.
For example, certain of our websites may use “cookies” or other methods to monitor website usage. We
may collect information on what games are played, how much time is spent playing the games, and which
ads or links are clicked. We may link cookie information to personal information.
Certain of our websites use an outside ad company to display ads. These ads may contain cookies.
Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and Hi-Rez does not have access
to this information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website.
You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, some
areas of the Services will not function properly if you do so.
Other technologies used in our websites include clear GIFs and IP address logging. Clear GIFs (i.e., web
bugs, beacons, or tags) are small graphic images placed on a webpage, web-based document, or in an
email message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (e.g., only 1-by-
1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the web page, document, or e-mail message. We do not
use clear GIFs to collect personal information about you. However, we may use clear GIFs to capture
statistical usage information for our webpages, features, or other elements on a webpage. We may
correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user
experiences on our webpages.
Hi-Rez also maintains log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is
assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). In general, we only use log files to
monitor traffic on our websites, to report aggregate information to our advertisers and third party service
providers, and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of user abuse of the Services; however,
we may block certain IP addresses, console IDs, device IDs, or other IDs provided by the applicable
licensed hardware manufacturer(s). IP addresses, console IDs, device IDs, and/or other IDs may be used
to personally identify you in order to enforce our Online Terms of Service and Use Agreement.
What Happens to the Information Provided?
Hi-Rez does not disclose any personal information about children under eighteen years of age who have
registered on any of our websites to third parties, regardless of parental consent, or share or disclose
personal information other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy; provided, however, that in the event of a
merger, acquisition, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, visitor and user information
(including, without limitation, personal information) maintained by Hi-Rez may be transferred to its
successors or assigns.
Users who register for an account with Hi-Rez may register for other services from our Site from time to
time. If you opt-in to any of these services, we may collect additional information including, without
limitation, information requested by a service provider, and pass this information, together with all other
registration information (including, without limitation, personal information), to that service provider. Use of
your personal information by a service provider will be governed by that service provider’s privacy policy
and terms of service. We may also retain any additional information collected for use in accordance with
the terms of this Privacy Policy. Participation in these other related services is optional and is not required
to access our Site.
The personal information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features, and
enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; and contests and events of interest. We may send
emails that may contain information regarding third party products or services; however, this does not
mean that we have provided or traded your personal information to any party.

We may use survey information in marketing surveys to select and direct advertising that is more likely to
be of interest to a particular user of an account with Hi-Rez. This information may be transmitted to an ad
server owned by an advertising company to match account holders with ads that they are more likely to
be interested in. However, we do not disclose any account holder’s personal information to our
advertisers without the holder’s consent. Participation in such surveys is entirely optional. We may share
aggregate consumer data (which does not contain personal information) with the advertising companies
or with any other third party, and we may use such information for any legitimate business purpose in our
sole discretion.
We may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can
consistently improve our websites to better meet our visitors’ and users’ needs. In addition, we may use
your personal information to enforce legal rights and comply with the law, or to comply with an order from
a judicial or government entity or other competent authority, or when we have reason to believe that a
disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property,
operations, users, or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage. Finally, we may also
disclose personal information to law enforcement, or the appropriate judicial or civil authorities.
Where is the Information Held?
Currently, Hi-Rez maintains and stores your personal information on servers located within the United
States. This may not apply to Hi-Rez’s third party providers (including, without limitation, Valve
Corporation, Microsoft Corporation, Sony Computer Entertainment, Inc., Sony Computer Entertainment
America LLC, Sony Computer Entertainment Europe Ltd., Apple Inc., Google Inc., and our third party
payment processors). In the event that Hi-Rez becomes a global organization with offices outside the
United States, some of the computer systems on which Hi-Rez collects, stores, and uses the information
it collects or receives may be based outside the United States. Therefore, your personal information may
be transferred to, used, processed, or held by Hi-Rez in the United States and in other countries,
including, without limitation, countries both in and outside the European Union, and used for the purposes
set out in this Privacy Policy. You hereby consent to such use.
Opt-out Provision
When we first collect information about you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your
personal information shared with parties outside of Hi-Rez or its Affiliates or its third party providers (such
as Valve Corporation and our payment processors), except to the extent required by law, court order, or
as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. If you choose to have your name
removed from our mailing list, you can do so by contacting our Data Privacy Officer at
privacy@hirezstudios.com.
Safeguarding Your Personal Information
We will only collect and use personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy to the extent
deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will use commercially
reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the security, integrity, accuracy,
and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that
third parties to whom we transfer any personal information will provide commercially reasonable
protection of that information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you
transmit to Hi-Rez, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Hi-
Rez makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of such information on our systems.
However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed,
altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, managerial, or other safeguards.
If Hi-Rez learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you
can take appropriate protective steps. Hi-Rez may post a notice on its Site if a security breach occurs.

Review and Correction of Your Information; Requests for Removal from Mailing Lists; and
Deactivating Your Account
If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by Hi-Rez is not correct, or
should you wish to have your account(s) deactivated or be removed from our mailing list, please email our
Data Privacy Officer at privacy@hirezstudios.com describing, in reasonable detail, the nature of the
request, problem, or concern. We will then review, update, or remove information as appropriate within a
commercially reasonable time frame after receiving such notice from you. We may still retain your
information in our electronic data or other files, however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user
agreement(s) and/or policy(ies), and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to
the security, integrity, and operation of our websites.
Display Advertising
Hi-Rez uses the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting features of Google Analytics for
Display Advertising. You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google
Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Preference Manager, which is available at
<https://www.google.com/settings/ads>.
Hi-Rez encourages visitors to read about the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, which is available
at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.
Hi-Rez and Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third party cookies
together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to Hi-Rez websites. This means that
vendors, including Google, will display Hi-Rez promotional material on other websites you visit across the
Internet. Hi-Rez also analyzes aggregate information provided by Google Analytics to determine usage
trends, which allows us to improve our websites and make it easier for you to find what you need.
California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights
Under California law, California residents who have an established business relationship with Hi-Rez or its
Affiliates may choose to opt out of Hi-Rez’s disclosure of personal information about them to third parties
for direct marketing purposes. As detailed in this Privacy Policy, our policy is not to disclose personal
information collected online to a third party for direct marketing purposes without your approval. If you
choose to opt-out at any time after granting approval, email our Data Privacy Officer at
privacy@hirezstudios.com or write to our Data Privacy Officer, Hi-Rez Studios, Inc., 3750 Brookside
Parkway, Suite 200 Alpharetta, Georgia 30022.
